<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Omnibear</title>
    <link>https://omnibear.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Omnibear</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:25:40 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://omnibear.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>https://omnibear.com/troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:25:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omnibear.com/troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description>It takes a lot of moving parts to get an IndieWeb site working. Omnibear offers logging to help you troubleshoot any issues when authenticating to your site or posting to your micropub endpoint.
Enable logging Go to the settings page and check the box labeled &amp;ldquo;Record debug logs&amp;rdquo; to enable logging.
Unchecking this box and saving settings will delete existing logs. “Info” and “warning” logs will not be saved while it is unchecked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Omnibear version 1.1.0</title>
      <link>https://omnibear.com/releases/1.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 11:53:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omnibear.com/releases/1.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Available now in Chrome and Firefox, or download it directly.
 added logging option to settings to enable better support/debugging fix reply-to posts posting as regular notes no longer require &amp;ldquo;me&amp;rdquo; parameter in authorization response fix errors when fetching syndication endpoints   Also posted on IndieNews</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Omnibear version 1.0.0</title>
      <link>https://omnibear.com/releases/1.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 12:12:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omnibear.com/releases/1.0.0/</guid>
      <description>Available now in Chrome and Firefox, or download it directly.
 Updated user interface Automatically saves draft Customizable user settings:  Automatically generate slug Always open in &amp;ldquo;reply to&amp;rdquo; mode Customizable Reacji &amp;amp; quick replies Customize micropub fieldnames (legacy support) Manually set micropub endpoint and token  Select syndication targets (NOTE: you may need to log out and back in after the update takes effect) Improved error messaging   Also posted on IndieNews</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Omnibear version 0.6.1</title>
      <link>https://omnibear.com/releases/0.6.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 15:22:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omnibear.com/releases/0.6.1/</guid>
      <description>Fixed add-on icon in Firefox added &amp;ldquo;reacji&amp;rdquo; support to quickly reply with an emoji improved error messaging   Also posted on IndieNews</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Omnibear version 0.6.0</title>
      <link>https://omnibear.com/releases/0.6.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 13:33:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omnibear.com/releases/0.6.0/</guid>
      <description>Verified working in Chromium and Vivaldi Character count is shown while writing a post Displays the url after a post is created (non-Chrome browsers only)   Also posted on IndieNews</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://omnibear.com/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 15:27:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omnibear.com/features/</guid>
      <description>Posting Omnibear is a MicroPub client, allowing you to publish posts to your website from anywhere on the web. Click on the browser extension icon to open the drafting window. Use this to compose and save your post.
Replying You can also post a reply to anything on the web. Right-click and select “Reply to entry” to write a reply. This will reply to the current URL.
If the current page is published with valid microformats, you can reply to any “h-entry” on the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Omnibear version 0.5.3</title>
      <link>https://omnibear.com/releases/0.5.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 15:27:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omnibear.com/releases/0.5.3/</guid>
      <description>With this release, Omnibear works in Firefox. Unfortunately, there is still a little bit of cleanup to do in order to get it accepted into the Firefox Add-on store, but if you are comfortable doing a dev install on your own, you can give it a test run.
Other changes:
 Fixes issues finding and highlighting the h-entry when right-clicked. Includes some permissions fixes to try to get Omnibear working in other browsers besides Chrome   Also posted on IndieNews</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>